Guide to the Rice University Photograph Files, 1910-2015 UA 363
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Individual photographs (Rice related individuals)
  - Vaughn, William S.
  - Veletsos, Dr. Anestis Stravrow
  - Veltman, Lester
  - Vernon, Connie William
  - Vest, Marty
  - Vick, James Clayton
  - Viner, Jacob
  - Volterra, Vito
  - Von der Mehden, Fred
  - Von Weizsacker, Richard
  - Vongvanich, Tevin
  - Voswinkel, Mary
  - Waggaman, Adele
  - Wagoner, James
  - Walker, Cornelius
  - Walker, Curtis Howe
  - Walker, Wililam F.
  - Wallace, Carolyn Hooton
  - Wallace, Frank
  - Walters, Geoffrey King
  - Wann, Dr. Trenton W.
  - Ward, Dr. Calvin H.
  - Ward, Herbert
  - Warme, John E.
  - Waser, Jurg
  - Watkin, Ray
  - Watkin, William Ward
  - Weaver, Ralph
  - Webb, David
  - Weber, Rolf Felix
  - Wedemeyer, Phil
  - Weems, F. Carrington
  - Wehrung, Donald
  - Weichert, Rudolph Frederick
  - Weiser, Harry Boyer
  - Westheimer, Alan D.
  - Westheimer, David
  - Wheeler, Joseph D.
  - Whitaker, Gilbert R.
  - White, Rex H.
  - White, William Erikson
  - Whitehill, Clifford L.
  - Whitmarsh, Robert L.
  - Whitmire, Kathryn
  - Whitmore, Dr. Frank Clifford
  - Wiener, Martin
  - Wierum, Frederic
  - Wiess, Harry / Olga
  - Wilder, Amos N.
  - Wilkin, George E. Jr.
  - Williams, Donald L.
  - Williams, George
  - Williams, J.M.
  - Williams, James A.
  - Wilson, Bill
  - Wilson, Harold Albert
  - Wilson, James L.
  - Wilson, Robert W.
  - Wilson, Stephen Gill
  - Wilson, Woodrow
  - Windham, Marivonne
  - Windsor, Duanne
  - Winkelmann, Fannie Gayle
  - Winningham, Geoff
  - Winters, Francis
  - Wischmeyer, Carl
  - Wise, Elizabeth Reynolds
  - Wise, Scott
  - Wisoff, Peter J.
  - Wojecki, Eddie
  - Wolda, John
  - Wong, Mark
  - Woodring, Carl
  - Woodson, Benjamin N. "Woody"
  - Woodyard, Kenneth Eugene
  - Worley, William E.
  - Worthington, Bauman (W.B. "Bill")
  - Wynne, Carole Riggs
  - Yagi, Sakae
  - Yaniv, Dr. A.
  - Yarborough, Don
  - Yim, Bennett
  - Young, Richard
  - Young, William James
  - Younts, James Ogden
  - Zansitis, Richard A.
  - Zeff, Stephen
- Series II: Group photographs (Rice people, places, things)
  - Abercrombie, Josephine E.
  - Abercrombie, M/M James and & Herb Allen
  - Akers, Dr. and Margaret "Sully" Alsobrook
  - Alborn, Ray & (unidentified)
  - Alumni - General, Multiple
  - Alumni Groups
  - Alumni Office Staff
  - Anderson, Mr. & Mrs. Ben
  - Architecture Faculty
  - Army ROTC
  - Art & Art History Dept.
  - "Arts at Rice" - Westheimer, Williams, Graves, Goyen
  - ASME (American Society of Mechanical Engineers) Rice Branch
  - Association of Rice Alumni Staff 1990
  - Astronaut Candidates, 1990
  - Baker College Cabinet meeting
  - Baker, James; McDowell, Carl; Rupp, George; Duncan, C.
  - Band (from Campanile + 1 from Janus)
  - Band Performances (not MOB)
  - Bands - Early
  - Bands - Jazz
  - Bands (Rice Institute, 1921) and others
  - Bands - MOB (2 folders)
    MOB with Rolligon Corp.
  - Bands - Parades
  - Bankhead, Bessie with Dr. E.O. Lovett
  - Bedenh, Joe and Baseball Coach
  - Berry, Michael and Student
  - Biochemistry Faculty
  - Bioengineering Faculty
  - [Rice Institute] Biological Society, 1916
  - Biology Dept. Faculty
  - Blanton, Mr. Ben and Miss Pender Turnbull
  - Blayney, Dr. Thomas Lindsey and Nell Mills
  - Blayney, Thomas Lindsey, and J.T. McCants
  - Board of Governors and Trustees (and Faculty)
    Faculty 1912
  - Board of Trustees
  - Bochner, Dr. Salomon and Robert Q. Sheldon
  - Boles, John & Others
  - Boles, John/Patten
  - Boles, John & Students
  - Bray family
  - Bremen, German Delegation to Rice
  - Brotzen, Franz & Frances with Hyman, Harold & Ferne
  - Brown & Root
  - Brown, George and Professor Hartsook
  - Brown, George R.
  - Brown, George R. and George J. Lacy
  - Brown, George R. and Tom Wier
  - Brown, Watson and Norman Hackerman
  - Bryan, A. and Roschach, H.
  - Burke, Jack & Ira Gruber & Gale Stokes
  - Burrus, Sid & students
  - Bush, George Herbert Walker and Sports Officials
  - Canterbury
  - Carbon 60 Team
  - Carrington, Sam and Others
  - Cattell, Jacques
  - Chamber Orchestra in Germany and Austria, 1970
  - Cheerleaders
  - Chemistry Dept.
  - Civil Engineering
  - Clark, Dr. H.C., Glenn E. Fryer, and Paolo Gasparini
  - Class of 1916
  - Class of 1919
  - Class of 1920
  - Class of 1924
  - Class of 1925/50th Reunion 1975
  - Class of 1926/50th Reunion 1976
  - Class of 1938/40th Reunion
  - Class of 1940 Reunion
  - Class of 1943 Reunion
  - Class of 1945/50th Reunion
  - Class of 1947
  - Class of 1951 Reunions
  - Class of 1958
  - Class of 1961
  - Club 13
  - Cohen, M/M, Pres. & Mrs. Houston, Pres. & Mrs. Pitzer
  - Colish, Etta Moselle & ??
  - College Bowl Champs 1982
  - College Masters
  - Collier, Everett and Mrs. William C. Morris
  - Computational and Applied Mathematics Dept.
  - Computer Science, Dept. of
  - Conoco Scholarship Selection Committees
  - Cooper, Joseph and David Brady
  - Cooper, Joseph and H.G. Dulaney
  - Cooper, Paul and Shirley Trepel
  - Craig, Dr. and Mrs., 1971
  - Crate, Prof. Harry, Eric Ashley, Omar Alsaad
  - Crowds
  - Cullinan, John and Craig
  - De Braemaker, Jean and Students
  - Dean, Alice Crowell and Mrs. Sara Stratford
  - Debate Team
  - Demme, Genevieve/husband
  - Dennis, Mr. and Perkins, Mr.
  - Dessler, Dr. A.J. and Dr. Fred S. Keller
  - Dissil, Henry and Jo Claire
  - Dramatic Club - "Green Stockings" cast, 1918
  - Drew, Dr. Katherine; Emison, Mr. Sam S.; Hobby, Mrs. William P. Jr.; Willoughby C. Williams
  - [Professor] Ducharme, Professor John K. Howell and students, 1973
  - Duncan, C.W. - Secretary of Energy
  - Dunlevie, Burce and Frank Vandiver
  - Economics Dept.
  - Education Dept.
  - Edwards, Edgar O. and Professor Leslie Wright
  - Electrical Engineering Dept.
  - Elizabeth Baldwin Literary Society
  - Engineering Class - Jan. 1924
  - Engineering Drawing Dept. Classes (Dummy Folder)
  - Engineering Society, 1924-25, 1925-26
  - English Dept.
  - Environmental Science & Engineering
  - Faculty
  - Faculty 1912
  - Faculty 1916
  - Fletcher, Richard and Robert Ford - Library Staff 1981
  - Fondren Library Staff
  - Football Coaches, 1930's
  - Ford, Robert and Tina Byrne - Library Staff 1981
  - Franklin, Joseph L.
  - French Senators
  - Freshmen
  - Friends of Fondren
  - [Rice University] Fund Council
  - [Dr.] Gallagher, Clark Moore, and Robert Timme
  - Gallagher, Jerold C.; Gary Philpy; Professor Davidson Akers; T.S. McPhail; S.R. Mut; M/A/ Brunbaugh
  - Gaylord, Dr. Thomas and Dr. Rabson, 1972
  - Geddes, Sir Auckland Campbell; Lady Geddes; Dr. E.O. Lovettl James A. Baker; Mrs James A. Baker
  - Geology and Geophysics Dept.
  - Geology Dept. Faculty
  - Gillis, Malcolm and Others
  - [Student] German Class 1912
  - Gorbachev & Djerejian
  - Gordon, William E.
  - Goyen, William, etc.
  - Gragg, Mr. and Mrs.
  - Graham, Shad and Emmett McGeever
  - Hackerman
  - Hackerman, Norman and Bill Hobby
  - Hackerman, Norman and Josephine Abercrombie
  - Hackerman, Norman and Gene
    Abercrombie, Josephine
  - Hackerman, Norman and Gene; James F. Lyon; Josephine Abercrombie
  - Hackerman, Norman; H. Malcolm Lovett; Harry J. Chavanne
  - Hamilton, Mr. and Mrs.
  - Hannah, David Jr. and Lecture Group
  - Hardy, Joyce Pounds & Others
  - Hartsook, A.J. and E. Butcher
  - Havens, Neal "Sandy" and Drama Students
  - Health and Physical Education Dept.
  - Henderson, Elizabeth P. and Frank C.
  - History Dept.
  - Homecoming Queen Candidates 1951
  - Hotung, Eric and Ross Rhone
  - Houston, Dr. William V. with students
  - Houston, Dr. William V.; Dr. Winfred Oliver Milligan; Dr. The Sveberd
  - Houston, Dr. William Vermillion
  - Houston, Dr. William Vermillion; Professor Floyd Lear; Arnold Toynbee; Professor Radislove Tsanoff
  - Houston, W.V. and Dallas Rice Alumni
  - Houston, W.V. and William Henry Masterson
  - Hudspeth, Mrs. C.M. and Mr. O'Keefe
  - Huxley, Julian
  - Hyman, Harold and Fern
  - Hyman, Harold M. and Katheirne F. Drew
  - ICSA
  - Idler's Club 1920
  - Jefferson Davis Papers Staff
  - Jones Business School
  - Journal of Southern History staff
  - Judge Peden and Lois Lee
  - Kemp. Lebbeus C., Jr. (Class of 1929) & Francis G. Winters (Class of 1944)
  - Kennedy, Ken + ?
  - Kennon, Elizabeth Rowe, Paul King, Alice C. Dean
  - Lacy, Bill N.
  - Lee's Owls
  - Ley, M/M Wendel
  - Library Cooperative Committee, 1945
  - Library Staff
  - Linguistics Dept.
  - Livingston, Larry, Jack Mazow, Michael Hammond
  - Lombardi, Cesar
  - Lovett Family
  - Lovett, Dr. E.O. and Capt. James A. Baker
  - Lovett, Dr. E.O. and Delegates, Jubilee of Sir George Gabriel Stokes, June 1899
  - Lovett, Dr. E.O. and Dr. W.V. Houston
  - Lovett, Dr. E.O. and Frank Thilly
  - Lovett, Dr. E.O. etc. in New Orleans, 1930's
  - Lovett, E.O. with other recipients of Princeton Honorary Doctorates, 1954
  - Lovett, Dr. E.O. and Harvard's President and Mrs. Lowell, 1922
  - Lovett, H. Malcolm and E.O. Lovett
  - Lovett, H. Malcolm and Gene Hackerman
  - Lovett, H. Malcolm and Martha
  - Lovett, Malcolm Jr. and H. Malcolm Lovett
  - Lovett, Malcolm with Geo. Rupp
  - Lovett, Zephaniah ("Grandfather" Lovett)
  - Maeterlinch, Mr. and Mrs. Maurice
  - Margrave, Dr. John L.
  - Masterson, Dr. and Dr. James Simms
  - Math Dept.
  - Matthews, Kathleen and Others
  - McCann, Samuel Glen and others
  - McCants, John Thomas
  - Mech Engineers, 1928
  - [Campus] Military Groups
  - Miller, Ray and others
  - Mitchell, Douglas et al.
  - Naval ROTC
  - Naval Science
  - Neeley, Jess, Ernie Coker, Dell Morgan
  - O'Keeffe, Richard and Diana Hobby
  - Old, Edythe Bates and Others
  - Oppenheimer, Ed and Herman, Gloria L.
  - Owen Wister Literary Society
  - OWL Literary Society
  - Patten, Bob & others
  - Patten, Bob & students
  - Pelli, Cesar with students
  - Phi Beta Kappa
  - Philosophy Dept.
  - Physical Plant Staff
  - Physics Dept.
  - Pitzer, Dr. Kenneth S. and Marwin Hurley
  - Pitzer, Dr. Kenneth S. and Members of GAC - Atomic Energy Comm.
  - Pitzer, Dr Kenneth & others
  - Pitzer, K.S. and Wife
  - [Rice University] Players
  - Police Dept.
  - Political Science Dept.
  - Portuguese and Classics Dept.
  - Pounds, Joyce & others
  - Pre-Med Society 1927
  - "R" Association
  - Rally Club
  - RAMAS (Richard Tapia and officers)
  - [Rice] Red Cross
  - Reiff, Patricia & ?
  - Religious Studies Dept.
  - Rice, Bill and Pat Quinn
  - Rice Center
  - Rice Chorale
  - Rice Computer Project
    Iliffe, John Kenneth; Martin Graham; Zevi Salsburg; John Kilpatrick
  - Rice Dance Troupe
  - Rice, David - Family
  - [William Marsh] Rice Family
  - [Photos by] Rice, Fred W. at Saranac Lake, New York 1875 - 1902
  - Rice University Press
  - Rorschach, Dr. and Chinese
  - ROTC
  - Royal Shakespeare Company
  - Rupp, George and Carl Macdowell
  - Rupp, George and Malcolm Lovett
  - Rupp, George and Mayor Kathy Whitmire
  - Rupp, George and Neal Lane
  - Sass, Dr. Ronald L.; Dr. John Herdklotz
  - Scott, Walter J. and Gene Sisb
  - Shaper, Sue and Allen Ley, Judy
  - Shepherd Quartet
  - Shepherd School Faculty
  - Shepherd School/Music performers
  - Shepherd School Musicians
  - Shepherd School Symphony Orchestra
  - Shepherd Singers
  - Sihvonen, Oli and students
  - [Dr.] Sims and Cpt. O. D. Dian
  - Sims, James R. & others
  - Smalley, Dr. Richard E.
  - Smalley, Richard and students
  - Smalley, Rick and others
  - Smith, Griffin and Libby
  - Smith, Richard J. and Chinese History Class
  - Sociology Faculty
  - Southwest Conference Development Officers 3-20-72
  - Space Physics and Astronomy, Dept. of
  - Space Science Dept.
  - SRUW Members
    Members: Hardy, Joyce; Worden, Helen; Zumwalt, Pat
  - St. Paul's Methodist Church, Rice Class of 1927
  - Stancliff, Mrs. Fred J. and others
  - Sterling, Robert and Jones School Faculty
  - Student Admissions Committee 1985
  - Student Army Training Corps (SATC)
  - Student Body
  - Students in the co-op
  - Students Pre-1930
  - Students Prior to 1950
  - Students - 1980s
  - Students-African-American Students (1970s)
  - Students-Athletics
  - Students-Beach
  - Students-Campanile Group Shots
  - Students-Dorm/Colleges
  - Students-Elections
  - Students-Freshman Week
  - Students-Freshman Week 1970
  - Students-Geology Expedition 1969
  - Students-Lab/Class
  - Students-Library
  - Students-Majors Day Preview 1972
  - Students-Misc.
  - Students-Outside on Campus (2 folders)
  - Students-Publishing Program, Summer 1979
  - Students-Recreation
  - Students-RMC
  - Students-ROTC
  - Students-Theatre
  - Students-Tutoring Program 1972
  - Students-Women's Lib 1970
  - Studies in English Literature staff
  - Tanning Club
  - Thomas, Norman and group
  - Thompson, Scott and athletes
  - Thresher
  - Tiger Inn Members, Princeton University 1902
  - Tsanoff, Radoslav
  - Tuggle, Francis and Grenias, George
  - Tuggle, Ikie, Mrs. Neihaus
  - Van Helden, Al and others
  - Vandiver, Frank E. and Dr. William H. Nelson
  - Vandiver, Frank E. and Harris Masterson and others
  - Vandiver, Frank E. and Radoslav Tsanoff
  - Vandiver, Frank; Karla Painter; Elaine Bonilla, 1977
  - Waggaman, Adele and others
  - Watkin, William Ward
  - Weber, Rolf Felix and unidentified girl
  - Westheimer, David
  - Wiener, Martina and William Brock
  - Wiess College Officers 1970
  - Wilson, Prof. Harold Albert and others
  - Wilson, Robert W. and others
  - [Rice] Women's Alliance
  - Women's Army Corps
  - Women's Glee Club
  - Woodwinds of Houston 10-27-71
  - [Professor] Young and students
  - YWCA 1916/17
- Series III: Campus building photographs
  - Abercrombie Hall (Engineering Lab building) - construction
  - Abercrombie Hall (Engineering Lab building) - exterior
  - Abercrombie Hall (Engineering Lab building) - interior
  - Allen Business Center - construction
  - Allen Business Center - exterior
  - Allen Business Center - interior
  - Anderson Hall - addition
  - Anderson Hall - architectural drawings
  - Anderson Hall - blueprint transparencies
  - Anderson Hall - construction
  - Anderson Hall - exterior
  - Anderson Hall - interior
  - Auditorium - exterior
  - Auditorium and Administration Building (proposed)
  - Autry House - exterior
  - Autry House - interior
  - Autry House - laying cornerstone
  - Autry House - proposed plans
  - Baker College (East Hall) - construction
  - Baker College (East Hall) - exterior
  - Baker College (East Hall) - interior
  - Baker College (East Hall) - plans
  - [James A.] Baker III Hall
  - Baker House
  - Banks Street Apartment for Rice Women
  - [M.D. Anderson] Biological Labs - exterior
  - Biology Building/M.D. Anderson Biological Labs - exterior construction
  - Biology Building/M.D. Anderson Biological Labs - interior construction
  - Biology Building Re-Roofing 1985 - 1986
  - Bonner Lab - destruction
  - Bonner Lab - exterior
  - Bonner Lab - interior
  - Brochstein Pavilion
  - [Margaret Root] Brown Coollege
  - [Alice Pratt] Brown Hall
  - [George R.] Brown Hall
  - [George R.] Brown Hall Biosciences - construction
  - Campus Police Station
  - Capitol Hotel - exterior
    See also: Rice Hotel
  - Car Shed for Trolley Shuttle, 1918
  - Chapel, Rayzor - construction
  - Chemical Engineering Laboratories
  - Chemistry Building - exterior and interior (3 folders)
  - Chemistry Building - interior
  - Chemistry Laboratories - construction
  - [Proposed] Classroom Building - rendering
  - Cohen House (Faculty Club) - architectural drawings
  - Cohen House (Faculty Club) - exterior
  - Cohen House (Faculty Club) - (new) exterior
  - Cohen House (Faculty Club) - interior
  - Cohen House (Faculty Club) - remodeling and construction
  - Community House
  - Cox Fitness Center
  - Dell Butcher Hall
  - Dormitories (men's) - exterior
  - Dormitories (men's) - interior
  - Dormitory, proposed, 1911
  - [Anne and Charles] Duncan Hall
  - [Old] Field House
  - [Old] Field House - interior damages, Dec. 1948
  - Flammable Substance Storage Facility
  - Fondren Library (new) construction
  - Fondren Library (new) exterior
  - Fondren Library (new) interior
  - Fondren Library (old) construction
  - Fondren Library (old) exterior
  - Fondren Library (old) interior
  - Fondren Library - exterior details
  - Fondren Library Interior Oct. 13, 1973
  - Fondren Library - Lecture lounge [Kyle Morrow]
  - Fondren Library - Music & Fine Arts Room [Brown Fine Arts]
  - Fondren Library - proposed building
  - Fondren Library Renovations 1987 - 1989
  - Fondren Library Renovations 2005
  - Fondren Library - Science Reading Room
  - Fondren Library - Stacks
  - Fondren Library - Staff Area
  - Fondren Library - Study Carrels
  - Founder's Room (formerly Faculty Chamber)
  - [Keith Weiss] Geological Laboratories - exterior
  - [Keith Weiss] Geological Laboratories - interior
  - [Keith Weiss] Geology Laboratory Bldg. Construction - exterior
  - Goodhue sketch, unidentified
  - Graduate House
  - [Rice] Gymnasium - exterior
  - [Rice] Gymnasium - interior
  - [Rice] Gymnasium - plans
  - Hamman Hall Auditorium - construction (exterior and interior)
  - Hamman Hall Auditorium - exterior
  - Hamman Hall Auditorium - interior
  - Hanszen College (West Hall) - exterior
  - Hanszen College (West Hall) - interior
  - Hanszen House
  - Heizer Sculpture Construction
  - Herman Brown Hall - construction
  - Herman Brown Hall - exterior
  - Herman Brown Hall - interior
  - Hermann Hospital
  - Herring Hall - exterior
  - [Jake] Hess Tennis Stadium, inauguration 1969
  - Humanities Building - construction
  - [Mary Gibbs] Jones College, north and south wings - construction
  - [Mary Gibbs] Jones College, north and south wings - interior construction
  - [Mary Gibbs] Jones College, north and south wings - exterior
  - [Mary Gibbs] Jones College, north and south wings - interior
  - Jones College Master's House
  - [Jesse H.] Jones School of Business Admin. - Construction
  - Ley Student Center
  - Lovett College - architectural drawings
  - Lovett College - exterior
  - Lovett College - interior
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - blueprints
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - construction
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - cornerstone, laying of
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - exterior (2 folders)
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - exterior (pre-1920)
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - exterior architectural details (capitals and columns)
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - exterior architectural details (cloisters)
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - exterior architectural details (heads/faces on capitals)
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - exterior architectural details (plaques)
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - exterior details
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - exterior negatives
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - interior
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - interior architectural details
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - interior Faculty Chamber
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - rendering
  - Lovett Hall (Administration Building) - snow scenes
  - Mail Services - Post Office
  - Martel College
  - McNair Hall
  - Mechanical Engineering Building - new building
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab and Power Plant - aerial view
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab and Power Plant - blueprints and plans
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab and Power Plant - construction
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab and Power Plant - exterior
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab and Power Plant - interior (2 folders)
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab and Power Plant - rendering
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab and Power Plant - rendering copy photograph
  - [Rice] Media Center
  - [Rice] Memorial Center - architectural rendering & construction
  - [Rice] Memorial Center - exterior: see Ley Student Center
  - [Rice] Memorial Center - interior: see Ley Student Center
  - Mudd Computer Building
  - Mudd Computer Building - construction
  - NAVY ROTC Building - exterior
  - Nichols-Rice-Cherry House
  - [The] Owl
  - Physics [Laboratory] Building - blueprints (copies)
  - Physics [Laboratory] Building - construction
  - Physics [Laboratory] Building - exterior
  - Physics [Laboratory] Building - interior
  - Power Plant - interior
  - President's House - construction
  - President's House - exterior
  - [Proposed] President's House - plans and copy photos
  - Princeton Observatory and House
  - [Rice] Quantum Institute
  - Rayzor Hall - construction
  - Rayzor Hall - exterior/interior
  - Reckling Park
  - Rice Recycling Center
  - Rice Hotel - exterior
  - Rice Hotel - interior
  - Ryon Engineering Lab Building
  - Sewall Hall - construction and dedication
  - Sewall Hall - exterior
  - Sewall Hall - exterior architectural details
  - Sewall Hall - interior
  - Sewall House - Blueprint Negatives
  - Sewall House - Exterior and Interior
  - Shepherd School of Music
  - Sid Richardson College - interior
  - Sid Richardson College - exterior
  - South College - old residential hall for men
    See also Will Rice College
  - Space Science Building - construction
  - Space Science Building - interior and exterior
  - [Football] Stadium (new) - aerial views
  - [Football] Stadium (new) - construction progress photographs
  - [Football] Stadium (new) - exterior
  - [Football] Stadium (old)
  - [New North Stands of Old] Stadium - construction
  - [Rice] Stadium - interior
  - [Rice] Stadium - proposals for roof
  - Stadium (track) interior
  - Warwick Hotel
  - Water Tank Interior
  - West Estate (Clear Lake) - exteriors (black and white)
  - West Estate (Clear Lake) - exteriors (color)
  - West Estate (Clear Lake) - interios (black and white)
  - West Estate (Clear Lake) - interiors (color)
  - Wiess College - construction
  - Wiess College - exterior
  - Wiess College - interior
  - Wiess College Commons - construction
  - Wiess House (Shadyside)
  - Wiess Master's House
  - Will Rice College (new) - construction
  - Will Rice College (new) - exterior
  - Will Rice College (new) - interior
  - Will Rice College (new) - plans
  - Will Rice College (South Hall, old) - construction
  - Will Rice College (South Hall, old) - exterior
  - Will Rice College (South Hall, old) - plans
- Series IV: Campus View, Interiors and Groups of Buildings photographs
  - Academic Court, Cloisters, Sallyport - aerial view
  - Academic Court - Construction
  - Academic Quad
  - Analytical Laboratory (Chemistry Building)
  - Anderson Hall and Arcade of Fondren Library
  - Anderson Hall Architecture Studio
  - Athletic Field
  - Autry Court
  - Baker College (East Hall), Administration Building (Lovett Hall)
  - Baker College, Lovett Hall, and Physics Building
  - Baker College Quad
  - Berlin Wall Piece
  - Billboard
  - Biological Lab
  - Bremen University
  - Brown Garden
  - Business Information Center (BIC)
  - Campanile Darkroom
  - Campus 1910
  - Campus (1912)
  - Campus 1913
  - Campus 1914
  - Campus 1916
  - Campus 1917
  - Campus (1920 or 1921)
  - Campus (1937)
  - Campus (circa 1950)
  - Campus 1970's
  - Campus 1980's
  - Campus aerial views
  - Campus aerial views (circa 1921 or earlier)
  - Campus aerial views (March - April, 1919)
  - Campus aerial views (Jan. 29, 1927)
  - Campus aerial views (Dec. 1, 1928)
  - Campus aerial views (1929)
  - Campus aerial views (Feb. or April, 1931)
  - Campus aerial views (April, 1933)
  - Campus aerial views (Summer, 1942)
  - Campus aerial views (1946 or 1947)
  - Campus aerial views (1948)
  - Campus aerial views (1950)
  - Campus aerial views (1953)
  - Campus aerial views (1956-57)
  - Campus aerial views (1963)
  - Campus aerial views (January, 1964)
  - Campus aerial views (1969)
  - Campus aerial views (1970's)
  - Campus aerial views (1980's)
  - Campus aerial views (1989)
  - Campus aerial views (1990)